Love Is All
Episode 07
Tan Lingyin made the jar by herself
Don't trust Tang Tianyuan and make the bet with him
My lord.
Look.
What are you doing?
I don't know either.
Yuner and her mother sent this to us.
It's to thank you and adviser's help for saving their lives.
I said no.
But they put down the present and left.
What shall we do?
Roast duck with soy sauce.
Wait. No spicy.
My lord.
We have a chef in our office.
If you think he's not qualified,
we can find you a new one.
When my lord was cooking,
he was thinking.
This is the new rule of the county office.
Do not disturb him.
Right.
It's our lucky to have such a lord
who love cooking.
My lord, do whatever you want.
No one will disturb you.
Officer Zheng, this is out of line.
For our lord,
even woman can be an adviser.
The rules have been already stewed as meat
by our lord.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
If you are tired or hungry,
you can tell me.
I will cook for you every day, okay?
Thank you.
Okay.
Why are you eating and drinking,
and I need to transcribe the files?
Because you are my adviser.
It is your duty.
It smells so good.
Look, my lord.
These are all old cases.
They are all closed.
Can I transcribe them in another day?
No.
There are so many tomorrows.
I quite! I want to eat!
Your honor said no. Don't you hear that?
I will sue you for abusing your subordinates.
Beat the imperial drum, do you understand?
If you don't,
go to find Li Dawang.
Let him teach you.
It smells so good.
My lord.
Wine and animals are ready.
Didn't I ask you to
throw them away before?
I...I...
My lord. I don't know what the monster is.
It kicked me out just by one kick.
Are your broadswords and sticks
just for show?
My lord.
What Xiaoliu said is all true.
It is even more cunning
than Zhang Zhiyuan
of Tian Xiang Club.
Really? Let me have a look.
So cute.
My lord.
No way.
I didn't say anything yet.
I say no even you didn't say.
Why are you so stingy?
You can give it to me.
Fine.
In here, you and this stuff,
only one can stay. You choose.
But I'm a female adviser.
I need a bodyguard.
How about we give it a three-day trials?
Okay. But we don't need
the trash who doesn't do anything but eat.
If you can't domesticate it in three days,
you'll leave with it together.
Don't worry.
I'm sure it'll be well-trained.
The feather is everywhere.
Come here.
You look as strong as me.
Then take my last name.
I'll call you Tan Baba.
Whatever you want to eat all my treat.
You can't touch this.
Except for this.
I'll cut the vegetable for you.
Wait for me.
Oh, no.
It's just a jar.
I'll compensate you one.
Compensate? How can you compensate me?
This old jar is a collection of the best quartz
from the Kanto region,
and the best feldspar from Luoyang Xijing.
It's fired by dalbergia odorifera and rosewood.
It's the only one in the world, the only one.
How can you compensate it?
For the past 3 years,
your honor only eats soup which cooked by this old jar.
Isn't it just a small jar?
Why so serious?
How can a vulgar man
know the feeling?
You elegant man are so hypocritical.
What did you say?
Nothing.
It's my fault. Please punish me.
What kind of punishment will restore this old jar?
It's fine.
Ask Xihulu to come and clean up.
Yes.
Don't get your hand hurt.
It's all your fault.
So clumsily.
It's all your fault. Tan Baba.
Sis.
You've been up all night
just for imitating his handwriting.
This fan.
We have to sell a dozen books to get it back.
Does it look similar?
Right, sis.
Did Magistrate Tang really know your identity?
He didn't blame you
or let you take the responsibility?
No.
It seems like he knew it long time ago.
But he said nothing.
He knew your real identity,
but he didn't blame you.
It means he knows what is the right and wrong.
Why do you always pick on him?
No, I don't.
Just a fan.
Besides.
I'm imitating Tong Tianyuan's signature.
Not him, Tang Feilong.
Why will he be angry?
When I've made enough money,
I'll go back to the capital,
and find Tang Tianyuan.
What are you thinking?
I didn't expect that
out adviser Tan is Miaomiaosheng.
Every injustice has its perpetrator and every debt its debtor.
May I ask how will you punish her?
Punish her.
We just find out the truth of the Qi Hui's case.
And the origin of the bad gold has not been found yet.
I don't have time to think about that.
You always have a point.
How's the investigation I asked you to do?
Assistant Zhou, he is clear.
As he said,
he has waited for years
to take this position.
About adviser Tan's situation,
you know much better than me.
The same as your Baba.
My Baba?
It's her Baba!
So should we keep investigating?
I think the most important thing right now
is to find out the truth of the gold mine case.
Miss.
Look at this one.
Fine texture, exquisite workmanship.
It's even unique in Tongling.
Do you like it?
If you don't like them all,
then we have no more good stuff.
Thank you.
Come again.
Have a look.
Please have a look.
Here you are.
I'm here.
Find out what the relationship
between the female adviser and Tang Feilong is.
Adviser Tan.
Fresh vegetables.
You are?
Why are you so upset?
What can I help you?
There's something wrong with this gold.
What? Do you think it's too little?
As the saying goes,
70% is cyan; 80% is yellow; 95% is red. This is cyan.
We can barely call it gold.
What's wrong with it?
The gold color made by the court
should not be like this.
Only those small workshops from underclass
will make something like this
because they don't have the skills.
Underclass?
You mean
what Sun Bufan said is true.
Qi Hui and Sun Bufan are both from rich families.
I don't think they will use somthing like this
to fool people.
Right.
Speaking of the gold,
only adviser Tan cares about it the most.
By the way, how about her bookstore?
It is really good.
Anything related to earn money,
every sec is important for our adviser.
Right. When the Qi Hui's case is closed,
the Volume One of Detective Series has come out.
I have to say that
our adviser Tan does things in moderation.
She didn't mention anything that she shouldn't in the novel.
But she said a lot of words
to praise you.
Isn't it all true?
You must feel sweet now.
Right.
The Gutang Bookstore is in a competition.
Turns out the fairy girl
who officer Zheng talks about is you.
Just call me Ruyi.
Although officer Zheng is careless,
he's serious to relationship.
You are so kind
to make a jar by yourself.
It's my fault to break the jar.
I need to compensate him a new one.
Magistrate Tang cares about it so much.
I searched all over Tongling.
And I didn't find any good five-color porcelain.
Actually the clay of the old jar is not expensive.
It's just not easy to find.
But there's a kind of clay on top of Mount Tianmu.
Although the quality is not as good as this,
if it's fired properly,
it will probably be 70% to 80% similar to the original one.
Really?
Did you know each other in the capital?
Gem!
We are so lucky.
Good.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Nice to see you here.
The Couplet Competition, sponsored by Gutang Bookstore,
will begin.
Please come on stage.
Okay.
This is our first line.
The phoenix falls on the sycamore,
the sycamore falls on the phoenix.
This is the competition you said?
Yes. The literature competition is also a competition.
I'll do it.
A pearl joins a jade and a jade joins a pearl.
Good.
The mountains are linked by water and the moon,
the water is linked by mountains.
Good.
The boat follows the tide,
the waves follow the boat.
Good.
the wind shakes the willow flakes,
the willow shakes the wind.
Good.
That's our Tongling's top four talents.
They're all the same.
Not only your second lines are similar,
but also your preference.
They're all fans sold by our Gutang Bookstore.
Of course.
My lord.
Assistant Zhou?
I think the Sun Bufan's case
needs to be opened again.
Then what do you think?
You should remember my mistake.
If I had given the hosts the convenience,
I will not be a little assistant in a small country.
I regret it all the time, my lord.
You are new here and has no foundation.
If you want to be a good magistrate,
the most important thing is
be nice with the nobles of the county.
Why don't you give convenience
to landlord Sun by this case?
I'm sure he will be grateful to you.
But Sun Bufan confessed to killing a man
in front of everyone.
It is hard to
appeal against his conviction.
This.
Sun Bufan killed her for a reason.
Please send him into exile instead of the death penalty .
And he can wait for the pardon.
It is okay.
How much did you get from them?
My lord.
How do you know?
I did receive some money.
But all I considered is for you.
If you think I'm wrong,
I will give you half of the money.
Two hundred taels.
Four hundred taels.
This number is bad.
My father is sick.
And my mother is old.
Fine. I won't take yours.
Did you see adviser?
No.
Find her.
Tell her to come to the study.
Mr. Tan?
You haven't slept yet.
What are you doing?
My sister wants to watch fireworks.
I'll make one for her.
Do you know how to do it?
Just follow instructions in the book.
Mr. Tan, you are so kind.
No matter what sister Lingyin wants,
you can make them for her.
My lord!
Where have you been to earn money?
What do you mean?
Seems like you take huge advantages of my fan.
You knew it.
But that is fake.
So.
You admit you copied my fan.
It's enough to pass off the fake as the real thing, right?
Why?
Paintings of masters will be imitated
by future generations sooner or later.
I was just one step ahead.
It's not upright to make a fake.
Good things should be shared with each other.
The fan with you
only makes you happy.
And now, everyone is happy.
You are so cunning.
I make money on my own way.
You only care about the money.
I don't wanna talk with you now.
If I only care about the money,
why should I give you this?
Little Huang also needs a drinking bowl.
This is perfect for it.
I'll give you the fan back tomorrow.
Save it to yourself.
I will not take back the thing I give.
What's wrong with you and adviser?
How should I know?
I just broke a jar. Why is she so angry?
The jar.
Adviser has been working hard for days
to make this jar.
You. You just broke it like that?
She made it herself?
There's only one woman in our office.
You should go to the bookstore more often,
and take more care of adviser's daily activities.
That's a pity.
Do not step on it.
I need to glue it up.
I really don't understand you.
I will leave now.
Come in.
Qingchen, you can't sleep at night?
Aren't you the one who's not sleeping?
My lord?
I will take you to a place.
Take me here to work in the midnight.
I am your adviser!
I am not your Muskmelon.
Are you still mad at me?
How dare I am?
Don't worry.
My bookstore is over there. I won't run away.
I'll pay you back
all the money of selling fans.
I want cash.
Normally, a man would just wave his hand
and say, "No, that's okay".
It's what you said to pay me back all the money.
Incense bags.
You're out of line.
Good-look incense bags.
Here you are.
I didn't know you made that jar by yourself.
Sorry.
It's me who broke your jar.
I should compensate you another.
But that one was broken.
I can't fix it anymore.
So I can only go to Mount Tianmu,
get some mud and make one for you.
You dug up the mud yourself?
Lady Zhou went there with me.
She's the beauty who officer zheng talked about.
I heard you want to go to the capital?
I want to go to the capital and see my Tang Tianyuan.
And then?
Say "thank you" to him.
That's it?
Didn't you say you wanna marry him?
I am a self-aware person,
okay?
So the novel this time you wrote
is still about him.
No. It's the story about you.
About what?
Don't be conceited.
I just use your life story
for convenience.
It's on fire!
It's on fire over there?!
Where is it?
What is going on?
It's on fire. Put out the fire.
Come on. Put out the fire.
What is going on?
It's on fire.
Put out the fire.
Come on.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Sis. Don't worry.
It's just the gunpowder exploded.
Why do you make gunpowder?
Didn't expect that your brother
had a hobby for inventions.
No.
It's because there's a popular romance novel said that
men and women need an atmosphere to get along.
And no woman could refuse a man
who would set off fireworks for her.
Bullshit.
Don't believe this crap.
Are you really okay?
The house burned down like this.
How about you live in the office?
Really?
Then what about my brother?
Sis, I can stay at hotel.
It's for free.
Together.
What about Fang and Zhuang?
The West Room is huge.
Thank you, my lord!
What's this?
Chicken soup?
My lord. It's been over one night.
Can't eat it anymore.
Autumn is coming. And it's cold now.
It's not that perishable.
Warm it up then send back.
My lord.
You never eat any overnight dish.
It's soup, not a dish.
Go.
Yes.
My lord, have some plum juice.
Hey guys! What's wrong with you?
Didn't I pay you?
Cry louder, louder!
Do you hear that?
That was scary.
My lord.
How many times did I tell you.
Don't yell.
And don't be too hard also.
We're not here to sing.
What are we doing here?
We're here to collect a debt.
I'll say it again. Listen carefully.
Concentrate the drool on the throat.
On the throat.
Follow me. One, two.
Right.
My daughter.
What are you doing?
They're gonna beat us!
The murderer's father is gonna beat us!
What's wrong with you?
My daughter will never come back.
I still have a disappointing son to raise.
My daughter, you just left.
When you're in Hades,
you must sue him.
Let Yama keep an eye on their family.
And make sure they'll die...
My lord. My lord.
Die painfully.
My lord, how about we just blow them away?
How?!
Do you think the young master is not guilty enough?!
My lord. My lord.
We've known each other for decades.
Stop acting.
The bureau for foreign shipping now needs a young director.
Your son is on the right age.
He's been sailing for years. You can ask him to come.
I'll give him this position. What do you think?
Just wake up.
Get me up.
What are you doing?
Wait. Wait.
My daughter was killed by your son.
I feel so painful. It really hurts.
Ridiculous. For your daughter?
If you do this for your daughter,
you should be in the county office now,
and ask Tang Feilong kill my son.
Are you here to get justice for your daughter?
You're looking for a way out for your son.
The county office is also a place of humanity.
I can apply for interceding as the father of Qi Hui.
Then Bufan can continue to
do filial piety to you.
Now you say something like a human.
Now you can tell me
if you'll be able to help
my son take the position of bureau.
Of course.
The point is if you can let it over.
My lord, vent one is hatred better than create more enemy!
Besides, we were friends for long time.
We're like a real family with each other, right?
Yes, my lord.
My lord.
Our families are going to rebuild our relationship.
Yes. We are now a family again.
Now, his daughter is gone.
Doesn't that mean
my daughter's gone?
Now my son Bufan,
if he is also gone,
then
it means your son is also gone, right?
Isn't it?
I can understand your feelings.
But why does it sound
like I killed your children?
I dare not.
Look.
This is a little gift.
My lord. What do you think?
But that is your daughter.
Right.
But my lord.
Bufan.
I've watched him growing up.
He is just like my half-son.
My daughter is already gone.
My daughter.
What's wrong, brother?!
Brother!
Brother. Are you okay, my brother?!
Impudence!
It is my duty to enforce the law impartially.
But if you get out of the county office,
and you still think I manage this county well,
work the case hard,
It's not too late
to give me these gold.
Thanks, my lord.
We understand.
The money from selling fans are all here.
You can count yourself.
Don't you wanna restructure your bookstore?
Take it.
I don't wanna use your money.
Dirty money.
What you said to landlord Sun,
I heard them all.
Landlord Qi asked for reconciliation.
So everything's ready now but my permission.
So you can lose your conscience,
take bribes and bend the law?
The case hasn't closed. I can't tell you anything.
You don't have to.
Now you are a corrupt official
in my heart.
I'll gather the evidence,
go to the capital and prosecute you. Wait for it.
Come back.
I, Tan Lingyin,
won't come back just because you tell me to.
Didn't you just come back?
Just for once.
Do you dare make a bet with me, Tan Lingyin?
For what?
If I can find a way to
not to offend landlord Sun,
and send Sun Bufan to the jail,
you need to promise me one condition.
A person who worships the golden calf like you.
How can I trust you?
Why do you talk so much?
Do you dare to bet or not?
Sure. Why not?!
If Sun Bufan can be executed,
I'll do whatever you want from now on.
But if you are gonna let him off the hook
for corruption,
you need to pay me double the gold he gave you.
Okay?
Okay.
But if you lose,
you need to pay me double.
Also, you need to say 3 words to me
in front of the whole county.
Say what?
My lord.
Are you...
Which three words do you think?
It's...
This is embarrassing. I can't say it.
If you lose,
say it to me
in front of everyone.
Do you wanna play fire?
Sure, I'm not afraid.
You're curious about that too.
I'm afraid you and your brother
will blow up the whole Tongling County again.
Is it that hard to be honest?
Don't you just have nothing to do?
Right.
Do you really think Sunjie's gold
is in Mount Tianmu?
Maybe.
Then shouldn't we
ask landlord Sun for something?
Ask what? The bet is not done yet.
It's too early to say anything.
If you have a way to balance Sun and Qi families
and win the bet,
why are you playing fire with me here?
Right.
Bring me that paper and writing brush.
For what?
Write the bet.
I'm afraid someone will deny if she lose.
Whatever. I'm not afraid.
You know you will lose, but you still wanna bet.
Is this a trap?
You won't come back anymore.
Now you're dead.
Don't blame me for paving the way for your brother.
Please bless your brother that his official career will be successful.
And blessing your father
goes smoothly.
Hui'er.
My lord, the carriage is ready.
I'm going.
I don't know
how much I owe my ungrateful son
in my life.
Recalling sad things is not good for your health.
You should take care of yourselves.
Brother, how about this.
Your daughter is died now.
No, she's not died. She will always be in my heart.
From now on,
our family Sun will always take your daughter
as my son's wife.
My son will always be your son-in-law.
He'll do everything he can for your family.
What do you think?
Right.
Son-in-law. Good son-in-law.
Let's toast to Magistrate Tang.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I don't drink.
But don't worry.
This case still has another way to deal with it.
Tang Feilong.
I'll record it all!
My lord. I have something to report.
What's wrong with you? Is there any outsider here?
My lord, this.
Just say it.
This inspector's team
has sent a handwriting order of the imperial envoy.
Imperial envoy?
Imperial envoy is coming.
My lord.
It says
the imperial envoy
received anonymous report
that I received a heavy bribe
and have collusion with merchant.
It also says that
Qi Hui's case
will be reported to the capital for rehearing.